（忆往昔）
这些盒子被施了咒
These are curse boxes.
它们封印着邪恶的魔法 对吗
They're supposed to keep the evil mojo in, right?
- 就像潘多拉宝盒 - 对
- Kind of like the Pandora deal? - Yeah.
这些是用来装受诅咒的物件的
They're built to contain the power of the cursed object.
萨姆 弗兰克正在破解
Sam, Frank's been working on the numbers.
鲍比用最后一口气写下的数字
that Bobby spent his last breath on.
是坐标
It's coordinates.
指向哪里
To what?
威斯康星州的一片野地
A field in Wisconsin,
刚刚被威廉公司收购
recently purchased by Willman, inc.,
而这家公司正是…
a subsidiary of…
如果你要赢 你就得是佼佼者
If you want to win, then you got to be the shark.
而大鱼吃小鱼
And a shark's got to eat.
理查德·罗曼企业旗下的子公司
…Richard Roman enterprises.
他们正准备建个什么东西
They're getting ready to build something.
- 要建什么 - 问得好 建什么
- Build what? - Exactly. What?
我就是个绝世怪物 但我能控制得了
I'm a grade-A freak, but I'm managing it.
现在绝对有什么不同了 不是吗
Something's definitely different now, isn't it?
- 你让我进去了 - 闭嘴
- You let me in. - Shut up.
他对我说「闭嘴」了
He said "Shut up" to me.
现在你以为还能用你小小的伎俩
So you think you can use your little tricks.
再这么赶走我吗 不行了
to banish me again, like that? No.
我确信我搞定你了 铺友
I do believe I've got you, bunk buddy.
（如今）
伊琳娜又没来
No Irina again.
她名气太大 我们不配和她一起练习
Guess she's too famous for us.
不是 她只是…
No, she just…
「香」独自练习
"vants" to be alone.
伊琳娜 现在练功有点晚吧
Irina. A little late for practice, no?
永远不会太晚
Never too late.
熟能生巧嘛
Practice makes perfect…
前提是你得有那天赋
if you have the talent.
[邪恶力量 第7季第16集]
迪克在资助一个考古挖掘项目吗
So, Dick's funding an archaeological dig?
除非迪克是想把自己挖出来
Well, unless Dick's actually digging himself,
我真不知这消息对我有啥用 弗兰克
I'm not sure I know what to do with that, Frank.
还有他在沙特阿拉伯的工厂
Or the factory in Saudi Arabia,
和雅加达的渔场
or the fishery in Jakarta.
这些都没啥用啊 弗兰克
None of this is helping, Frank.
从西方世界到东南亚是多大的范围啊
Explain how Western to Southeast Asia is too wide a net.
我本可去特罗姆瑟避难
You know, I could be in Tromso right now.
特罗姆瑟就没有利维坦活动
Zero Leviathan activity in Tromso.
特罗姆瑟在哪
Where the hell is Tromso?
在挪威 你这蠢蛋
Norway, you moron.
顺便说一下
By the way,
他们在比尤特又开了一家比格森连锁店
they opened another Biggerson in Butte.
知道了 但我们不在蒙塔纳州
Yeah, well, we're not in Montana.
真不容易 你知道比尤特在哪 真欣慰
Oh, you know where butte is. That's encouraging.
那么你们在哪呢
So, where are you?
- 我们在俄勒冈呢 - 不是吧
- We're in Oregon. - No.
我在俄勒冈什么都没查到
I got nothing in Oregon.
威斯康星啊 弗兰克
Wisconsin, Frank.
那怎么了
What about it?
那些坐标啊 鲍比给咱们的坐标
The coordinates … Bobby's coordinates.
鲍比
Bobby…
想起来了
Oh! Right.
对 没啥东西 没动静
Yeah, no. I got nothing. I got no activity.
那就再查查
Well, work on it.
你啥时候成我老大了
Hey. When did you become the boss of me?
你要是看不上我干的活
You don't like what I'm doing,
你就给我去死吧
you can stick it right up your Montana.
好了 好了 有话好好说 弗兰克
All right, all right, all right. Take it easy, Frank.
对 还有件事
Oh, and another thing …
弗兰克 喂
Frank? Hello?
弗兰…
Fr…
这个疯老头
He's a crazy son of a bitch.
是说弗兰克吗
Frank?
向一个暴躁的疑心病求助
You know, having a cranky total paranoid as your go-to guy.
真是…
That's … it's…
我都不知道该咋说了
I don't know what it is.
你这是干吗 要打破喝咖啡的
What, are you going for, like, the Guinness record.
吉尼斯纪录吗
of caffeine consumption?
这是你今早第五杯了吧
That's like your fifth this morning.
每当我一闭眼
Yeah, well, every time I close my eyes,
路西法就冲我大喊大叫
Lucifer is yelling into my head.
就好像我放他进来一次
It's like I let him in once,
就再也无法摆脱
now I can't get rid of him.
你知道他并不是真的…
You know he's not actually…
对 对 我知道
Yeah. Yeah, no. I know.
这话跟我脑袋里的音量控制开关说吧
Uh, try telling that to the volume control inside my brain.
你没再试试掐伤口那招
Well, did you try the hand thing?
试了
Yeah.
反正我现在清醒 看看这个
Anyway, long as I'm awake, check it out.
报道说是嗑药了 但你看看言外之意
They're saying drugs, but read between the lines.
她好像把自己的脚跳掉了
Sounds like she danced her own feet off.
有可能是咱们的事
Might be our kind of thing.
舞蹈演员
Dancers.
穿着芭蕾舞鞋的疯子
They are toe shoes full of crazy.
你…你怎么会有了解呢
You … and you would know this how?
我看过《黑天鹅》
I saw "Black Swan",
看了两回呢
twice.
激情四射的女同表演
Hot tutu-on-tutu action?
行了吧 萨姆 你什么毛病啊
Come on, Sam. What's wrong with you?
你可真有深度啊…
The depths of your…
这就在波特兰 几小时车程
Anyway, it's in Portland, a couple hours away.
你说呢
What do you think?
好 舞者嘛 何乐不为
Yeah, dancers. Why not?
说不定你在路上还能睡一觉呢
Maybe you'll get some sleep on the way.
也许吧
Yeah, maybe.
跟平常一样 没电磁干扰
So, the usual … no EMF,
没硫磺 没有巫蛊的东西
no sulfur, no hex junk.
如果这趟见不到几个舞者
If there's no more dancers to interview on this trip,
那就白跑了
it could be a bust,
但我听说波特兰的咖啡不错
although I hear they have good coffee in Portland.
伙计 那是西雅图
Dude, that's Seattle.
咱们还是先干正事吧
Oh, let's just get the drill over with.
什么事
Yeah?
我们想看看伊琳娜·考甘赞
Uh, we'd like to see the crime-scene photos.
死亡现场的照片
from the Irina Koganzon case, please.
你们是…
And you would be…
等一会
Give me a minute.
不急
Take your time.
亲爱的 你可不能碰这些
No, you can't touch those, honey.
这是爸爸工作用的东西
Those are for daddy's work.
爸爸
Daddy…
我想上厕所
I have to go pee.
亲爱的 你知道厕所在哪
Sweetie, you know where the little girls' room is.
对 是挺奇怪的
Yeah, I'd call that weird.
你好
Hey, there. How you doing?
好吧 你们想干吗
Okay. What can I do for you fellas?
我们要看芭蕾舞蹈演员
Well, we need to see the shoes.
死时候穿的那双鞋
that were involved in the ballet dancer's death.
没想到联调局会管这案子
Didn't figure that would be an FBI deal.
没问题 鞋就在这儿
But sure. Yeah, right here.
见鬼 翠西
Damn it, Tracy.
谁是翠西
Who's Tracy?
我女儿
My daughter.
她超爱芭蕾
She loves ballet.
快把那鞋脱掉
Hey, take those shoes off.
迪恩 快拿鞋
Dean, get the shoes!
我正在弄啊
I'm trying!
抱歉
Sorry.
快点 迪恩
Come on, Dean!
我在脱啊
I'm trying!
抱歉
Sorry!
拿下来了
I got it!
好了
Okay.
这肯定是受诅咒的物件
I'm going with cursed object.
还用说吗
You think?!
你没事吧
You okay?
下一站 旧的不去 新的不来
Next stop … Out with the old.
我想我们不能奢望这双鞋
I suppose it's too much to hope that these shoes.
是店里唯一的危险物品吧
are the only thing in that store that we have to worry about.
你真是天真的可爱
Oh, what a dreamer you are.
咱们不是把鞋放在后备箱了么
Didn't we put those in the trunk?
那是怎么…
H-how did they …
受诅咒的物件啊 萨姆
Cursed object, Sam.
这好像是你的鞋号啊
Do they…look like they're… your size?
闭嘴
Shut up.
等等 你…
Wait, a-are you …
有一种要忘我舞蹈的冲动吗
Getting the strong urge to Prince Siegfried myself into oblivion?
是的
Yes.
你还真看过《黑天鹅》啊
You really did see "Black Swan."
很高兴能跟你见面 马修先生
Well, it was nice seeing you, Mr. Marshall.
如果对我们的提议有疑问尽管打给我
Please call me if you have any questions about the offer.
我想好会联系你的
I'll let you know.
我想他不会卖的
I don't think he's gonna sell.
思考不是你的强项 乔治
Thinking is not your strong suit, George.
乔治
George?
开门
The door.
有人吗
Hello?
这是你卖的么
Hey, did you sell these?
对
Uh, yeah.
你从哪弄来的
Where did you get them?
我妈把它们放在那盒子里
Uh, m-my m-mother had them in that box.
我不明白 怎么了
I don't understand. What's happening?
这个吗 这里面的吗
This, in here?
天啊
Geez!
你还好吧 巴瑞辛尼科夫（芭蕾舞传奇巨星）
You okay there, Baryshnikov?
没事
Yeah.
还好 我「还好」
Yeah, I'm "pas de done."
如果不太麻烦
Okay, if it's not too much trouble,
你们能告诉我这是怎么回事吗
do you mind telling me, uh, what's … what's going on?
你叫什么
What's your name?
斯考特 斯考特·弗里曼
Uh, Scott … uh, Scott Freeman.
你说这些是你妈的吗
You said these were your mother's?
她从哪里弄到的
Where'd she get them?
不知道 我在后面找到的
I don't know. I found them in the back.
我去看看
I got it.
你母亲现在在哪里
Now, where is your mother?
她 她上周去世了
Well, she's, uh…she passed away last week.
节哀顺变
I'm sorry to hear that.
听着 斯考特
Scott, listen.
这双鞋子
These shoes…
不过是她收集的一些私人物品
Just some personal stuff she collected.
我正在想办法都给卖掉
I'm trying to get rid of it all.
都 还有其他类似物品吗
All? Is there more like this?
萨姆
Sam.
斯考特 那些盒子里原来有什么
Scott, what was in those boxes?
好吧 你们是哪门子联调局探员
Okay, what the hell kind of FBI guys are you?
为你收拾烂摊子的那种
The kind that are trying to fix the mess you started.
你妈妈在哪里弄到这些的
Now where'd your mom get these?
不知道 我在她的保险柜里找到的
I don't know. I found them in her safe.
你就从没想过这些东西
Did it ever occur to you that these things.
被锁在保险柜里可能是有原因的
might be locked in that safe for a reason?
没有 我以为那不过是
No, I just thought it was some of the junk.
她多年来收集的破烂
that she had collected over the years.
我知道她喜欢古怪的东西
Like, I knew she was into some weird stuff,
但我从来不知道她会
but I never thought that she would be, like …
你该好好考虑的
Yeah, well, think again, okay?
因为这些「破烂」在杀人
'Cause this "junk" is killing people.
- 什么 怎么可能 - 听着 斯考特
- What? Like, how can that be? - Look, Scott.
我们得知道你到底卖出了保险箱里的什么东西
We're gonna need to know exactly what you sold out of that safe,
以及买家的姓名和地址
and names and addresses of who you sold it to.
好吧 这个人是什么情况
All right, what do we got?
她买了一只茶壶
She bought a tea kettle.
- 茶壶 - 没错
- Tea kettle? - Yeah.
如果巫术够厉害 一只铅笔也能
Hey, with enough curse mojo, you can turn a freaking pencil.
变成大规模杀伤性武器
into a weapon of mass destruction.
流年不利啊
Good times.
最好打电话报案
Better call this in.
你好
Hello, yeah.
格汉姆大街23号发生了一起事故
I'd like to report an accident at 23 Gorham Road.
我的名字
My name?
是布鲁斯·宏斯比（知名音乐人）
Bruce Hornsby.
好了 下一个是谁
All right. Who's next on the list?
购买留声机的布兰达·格拉克
We got a, uh, gramophone sold to Brenda Gluck,
住在小河街413号
413 River Street,
以及购买旧《绅士杂志》的
and a vintage Gentleman's Magazine.
彼得·杨吉特 住在约翰逊巷27号
sold to Peter Yankit, 27 Johnson Lane.
- 不是吧 - 没错
- Really? - Yeah.
好吧 我们分头行动吧
All right, we'd better split up.
你去解决留声机
Why don't you take the gramophone?
我着手对付旧色情杂志
I'll handle the old rag.
如果我是你 可不会真的「着手」
I wouldn't really "handle" it if I were you.
记得那双鞋吗
Remember those shoes?
当然 怎么可能忘记
Yeah, how could I forget?
不知旧色情杂志是怎么杀人的
You know, I wonder how old porn kills you.
你肯定不会想知道的
Pretty sure you don't want to know.
- 你大概是对的 好了 出发 - 好
- Yeah, you're probably right. All right. Let's do this. - Yeah.
我把这些搬上楼 马上回来
I'm gonna run these upstairs. Be right back.
蒂姆
Timmy.
蒂姆 过来
Timmy, come here.
我要告诉你个秘密
I have a secret for you.
喂 蒂姆
Psst. Timmy.
过来
Come here.
蒂姆
Timmy.
留声机在哪里
Where's the gramophone?
别动 那是我的
Hey. That's mine.
小子 你正好借此机会知道什么叫感恩
Kid, this would be a really good time for a lesson in gratitude.
算你走运 我累了不想揍人
Lucky for you, I'm too tired.
我找到色情杂志了 很及时
Got the porn. Just in time, too.
他做什么了
What was he doing?
就像你说的 你不会想知道的
Uh, like you said, you don't want to know.
你进展如何
Where are you at?
我刚找到留声机
I just got the gramophone.
在小镇另一头 我去找你
I'm across town. I'll head your way.
这么说我妈妈不是疯子
So my mom wasn't just some whack job.
这些东西全是真格的
All this stuff is real?
没错
Yep.
我真是太歉疚了
Well, now I-I really feel like crap.
为什么
How come?
我一直敦促她卖掉小店
Well I kept pushing her to sell the store.
她总是不同意 而我继续催她
She kept saying no, and I kept pushing her,
跟她说能赚多少钱什么的
you know, telling her how much money she'd make.
你认为你让她改变想法了
You think you changed her mind?
我不知道
I don't know.
有位房地产公司的女士总来找她
You know, this real-estate lady kept coming around,
后来有一天 妈妈突然就同意了
and then one day, just like that, mom says okay.
然后她就出了事故
Then she had that accident,
甚至来不及享福
never even got to enjoy the money.
事隔多久
How soon after?
就第二天
The next day.
她怎么死的
How did she die?
车祸
Car crash.
我一直在想 如果我没有催她 那么
You know, I keep thinking, if I hadn't pushed her, then…
我跟你说啊
Hey, a little tip.
内疚也无法让死者复生
Feeling guilty ain't gonna bring 'em back.
你只能好好生活
Best you can do is live your life.
让她为你骄傲
the way that you think would make her proud.
至少别丢尽她的脸
Or at least not embarrass the crap out of her.
你知道该怎么做吧
You know the drill, right?
别碰箱子里的任何东西
Don't touch anything in those boxes.
事实上 你都不要靠近那个保险箱
In fact, don't even go near the safe.
我们把那些东西都装好箱
Once we get it all boxed up,
就叫辆货车来把它们都运走
we'll get a U-Haul and get everything out of here.
相信我 我懂的
Believe me, I… I got it.
（已售 碧科比地产）
马修先生 这个街区会大变样的
You know, Mr. Marshall, the block won't be the same.
你大部分邻居都已经卖了
Most of your neighbors have already sold.
我为你准备了一份分析报告
Now, I've prepared an analysis report for you.
乔治
George?
不是这份 乔治 马修先生的
Not this one, George. Mr. Marshall's.
如今要找个好帮手真心不容易啊
Hard to find good help these days.
好了 正如你所见
Anyway, as you can see,
我们的报价已经相当慷慨了
our offer is more than generous.
确实如此
Seems that way.
有了这一大笔钱
And with that generous offer,
你几乎可以随心所欲了
you can pretty much go wherever and do whatever you please.
你可以继续好好生活了
You can get on with your life.
碧科比小姐 我今晚来这
You know, Miss Bicklebee, I came here tonight.
本来是要卖掉那间铺子的
with every intention of selling.
但你刚才说什么继续好好生活
But what you just said, about getting on with my life…
那间铺子就是我的生活
That store is my life.
我不能卖
I can't sell.
我们都对过去恋恋不舍
Look, we all feel attached to our past,
但未来才是真正的冒险
but it's the future that's the real adventure, and…
抱歉 我不卖
Sorry, not sellin'.
我也不买你那套 女士
And I ain't buyin' that crap either, lady.
你要是拿定了主意 我也没办法
Well, if that's your decision, what can I say?
祝你余生好运
I wish you the best of luck with the rest of your life…
可惜你时日无多了
what little there is left of it.
看到没
See?
如预期的那样
As promised…
买到手了
on the dotted line.
怎么了
What?
你是不是太急着杀人了
Maybe you were a little quick on the trigger?
先是古董店的女人 现在又是这个
First the woman at the antique shop, and now this.
你知道罗曼先生
I mean, you know that Mr. Roman.
不喜欢我们太招眼
doesn't like us calling attention to ourselves…
我该怎么处理尸体
So, what should I do with the body?
没错 这态度就对了
There. That's the attitude.
好了
Okay.
把马修先生和他难闻的雪茄送回家
Take Mr. Marshall and his stinky cigar home.
把他放在床上
and put them in bed.
还有 乔治
Oh. And, George?
确保雪茄点燃了
Make sure the cigar is lit.
烧得火热
You know, burning hot.
马修先生死了 他应该戒烟的
There goes Mr. Marshall. Should've quit smoking.
吸烟有害健康
Can be hazardous to your health.
你知道自我占据这副身体以来
Do you know how many assistants I've had.
换过多少助理吗 乔治
since taking this body, George?
大概三个
Maybe three?
五个
Five.
你自行想象前四个的下场吧
I leave it to your imagination what happened to the first four.
咖啡煮得不好吗
Was something wrong with the brew?
你说呢 我要什么
You tell me. What did I ask for?
一杯热咖啡
A hot cup of coffee.
没错 咖啡的部分说对了
That's right. Got the coffee part.
但我说「热的」
But did I say "hot",
还是「温的」呢
or, I don't know, "tepid"?
有四个前车之鉴 乔治 随口说说罢了
Four, George. Just saying.
去主街的咖啡师那里
So go to that nice barista on main.
给我买一杯大杯的脱脂无奶油白摩卡
and get me a grande non-fat no-whip white mocha,
一泵无糖糖浆 双份特浓 好吗
one pump sugar-free, double-shot espresso, 'kay?
没问题
Sure.
那家店在镇子的另一头
Um, t-that's all the way across town.
- 我要九点才能回来 - 好 8点45见
- I won't be back till 9:00. - Okay. See you at 8:45.
什么事
Hey, what's up?
我就到了
I'm on my way.
我们现在还不能把保险箱带走
Yeah, not sure we're taking the safe out of town just yet.
- 给你 - 谢谢
- Here you go. - Thanks.
原来并不是囤积症妈妈百年之后
Um, so, it turns out that mama hoarder didn't just die.
斯考特继承了小店
and leave the store to Scott.
不是吗
She didn't?
不是的 听我说
No, listen to this.
她四十年来一直想留住小店
The lady spends 40 years trying to keep that place, right?
然后有一天她醒来就答应卖了
Then one day she wakes up and sells.
第二天就开车坠崖了
Next day, drives her car off a cliff.
怎么 你觉得
So, uh… what, you think.
有人割断了她的刹车吗
somebody cut her brakes or something?
不 我觉得世界真是充满了搞笑的巧合
No, I think the world is full of hilarious coincidences.
另外还有个新公司
Oh, and there's this new company …
听都没听过 做房地产的
never even tasted real estate,
把主街上的店面都要买光了
just gobbled up a huge chunk of main street.
现在下结论可能有点草率
Now, I could be off the deep end here,
但你不觉得奇怪吗
but doesn't that seem weird to you?
萨姆
Sam?
对对对 听起来不错 保持联系
Yeah. Yeah, yeah. sounds good. Keep me posted.
听起来不错
Sounds good?
你没事吧
Are you all right?
有人说过 不许人睡觉
You know, they said, um, sleep deprivation.
- 是一种「强大的审讯手段」 - 怎么了
- is an "enhanced interrogation technique"? - Yeah.
相信我 这根本就是酷刑
Trust me, it's torture.
（抱歉 该网站无法访问）
该死
Son of a bitch.
找我最好有好事
This better be good.
弗兰克 我倒是不想让你更加凌乱
Frank, hey, I don't mean to double-dip in your crazy sauce.
- 没别的意思 - 没事 你个软蛋
- No offense. - None taken, fudge pop.
我可能有发现
But I think I found something.
我不说话就是等着你说 迪恩
My silence is your cue, Dean.
波特兰这边有家新公司
All right, so, there's this new company.
正大举买下这边的小买卖
that's buying up a whole bunch of Mom and Pop's in Portland.
但我在登陆公司网站时被防火墙挡住了
But I hit a firewall when I tried to access its site.
你应该能破解吧
Think you can crack it?
你觉得狗会玩扑克吗
Can a dog play poker?
我不…
I don't…
当然可以 给我公司名称
The answer is yes. What's the company name?
兴隆地产股份有限公司
Uh, GEOTHRIVE, Inc.
慢着
Wait!
我说过只要一泵无糖糖浆 不是两泵
I said one pump sugar-free, not two.
另一泵是免费送的
Extra pump's on the house.
多谢好意 但是我老板尝得出来
That's very nice, but my boss is gonna be able to tell, okay?
请你重新给我做一杯
So please just make me a new one.
那么多人在排队 只有我一人在忙
There's people in line, and I'm here all alone, so…
好好享用这泵免费糖浆吧
Enjoy the free pump.
你还是给我重做一杯吧
How about make me a new one?
你吃了我得了
How about you eat me?
别逼我啊
Don't tempt me.
你走运了 我现在迟到了
You'are Lucky I'm late.
超级走运
So lucky.
下一个
Next.
我要份三倍超浓咖啡
Can I get a, uh, a-a triple red-eye, please?
你不要命了
It's your funeral.
你说些什么呢 乔治
What are you talking about, George?
我要的咖啡呢
Where's my coffee?
我是说真的 没开玩笑
I am seriously, not kidding.
你确定那是他吗
And you're sure it's him?
确定
Of course I'm sure.
萨姆·温彻斯特正迈进我们刚买下的古董店
Sam Winchester is going into that antique shop we just bought.
你觉得他们是来找我们的吗
Y-you think they're here for us?
不会 相信我
No. Trust me.
如果温家兄弟是来找我们的 我们会知道的
If the Winchesters were here for us, we'd know.
我肯定会很享受这个的
I am going to enjoy this.
享受 享受什么 乔治
Enjoy? Enjoy what, George?
我想我要吃掉他吧
Well…eating him is pretty much what I was thinking.
什么
What?!
- 不行 - 不行
- No! - No?
赶快回办公室
Come back to the office.
马上
Now.
我们是有管理系统的 乔治
We have a chain of command here, George.
你看到哪个温家兄弟了 你不能吃
You see a Winchester, you don't eat him.
你得告诉我 我来吃
You tell me, and I eat him.
你怎么想的 我还能告诉迪克
What do you think, I'm gonna tell Dick,
「他可能吃了他 但我没看到过程」
"I think he ate him, but I didn't see it"?
还要我给你作担保吗 乔治
What, I'm supposed to vouch for you, George?
你再干件蠢事就该自噬谢罪了
Like you're not one dumb move away from a bibbing already?
拜托
Come on.
但是我
But I …
别说了
Oh, no!
- 但是 - 闭嘴
- But… - No!
不许顶嘴
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
这是两泵
Two pumps.
不是吧 乔治
Really, George?
弗兰克 是不是有发现
Frank, tell me you got something.
我打电话是告诉你湖人对凯尔特的比分
No, I'm calling with the Lakers-Celtics score.
什么
What?
当然是有发现
'Course I got something.
我知道你为什么被防火墙拦下了
I figured out why you hit that firewall.
弗兰克 我不说话就是等着你说
My silence is your cue, Frank.
真会说话
Oh, touche?
你想要进入兴隆地产的内部网络
So, you were trying to access the GEOTHRIVE internal site,
之所以进不去
and the reason why you couldn't.
因为只要挖得够深
'cause if you dig down deep,
总是迪克在搞鬼
it's all Dick.
这倒是挺有用
Yeah, well, that'd be helpful.
问题是你什么事都往他身上扯
if you didn't say that about everything.
是 但我这里有真凭实据 机灵鬼
Yeah, except I'm operating on hard fact now, wise-ass.
你是说兴隆地产是罗曼公司一部分
So you're tellin' me that GEOTHRIVE is part of Roman, Inc.?
是这个联合企业中一个子公司的联合企业
It's a conglomerate within a subsidiary within a conglomerate.
都联系在一起了 迪恩
It's all tied together, Dean.
这算怎么回事 利维坦现在收购起小买卖了
Okay so what, Leviathans are Walmart-ting mom-'n'-pops?
回答正确加十分
And bingo was his name-o. Ahh!
那么威斯康星州有片荒地
So, we've got a big ol' field in Wisconsin.
波特兰又整了一堆小店
and a bunch of friggin' shops in Portland?
这帮人要干嘛啊
What the hell are they up to?
我不知道
Beats me.
我只知道它隶属迪克的公司而且绝对有蹊跷
All I know is it's corporate and smelly as the day is long.
我要是你 我就立马开溜
If I were you, I'd get out of dodge, pronto.
这里在出人命 弗兰克
People are dying here, Frank.
每秒钟都有人死 去查肥胖症统计数据吧
Sure, every second. Check the obesity stats.
那个小镇没啥特别的
That town ain't nothin' special.
我们还不能离开
Well, we're not done here, okay,
说不定能查到什么呢
and, hey, we might get some answers.
好吧
Fine.
有命活下来再打给我
Call me if you don't die.
- 怎么样 - 这辆就行
- So? - Well, that'll work.
怎么样了
Um, how's it going?
我刚跟弗兰克通过电话
I just got off the phone with Frank.
这镇上有利维坦在作怪
Apparently, we have a bit of a leviathan issue in this town.
- 这里有利维坦 - 没错
- Leviathan, here? - Yeah.
有一个迪克那样的老怪物
We're lookin' at a big, old giant nesting doll of Dick,
在地产销售界混呢
as far as property sales go.
听着我说话没
Hey, you hearing me?
听着了 抱歉
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah. I'm sorry.
行了 别再搞什么不睡觉了
Okay, you know what? Enough with the insomnia crap.
听着没 你得睡一觉了
All right, pacino? You need to crash.
我继续工作 你找个汽车旅馆睡一觉
I'll keep working. You find a motel and get some sleep. Okay?
我干嘛都没有 迪恩
It doesn't matter what I do, Dean.
路西法就是不闭嘴
Lucifer will not shut up.
现在也是吗
Even now?
他正在唱《天国的阶梯》
He's singing "stairway to heaven" right now.
好歌啊
Good song.
连听五十次就吐了
Not 50 times in a row.
喂 斯考特
Hey, Scott.
求你 萨姆 你得帮帮我
Please, Sam. Y-you got to help me.
出什么事了
What's happening?
我看了一眼我妈妈的一个旧镜子
I looked in one of my mom's old mirrors,
现在我想把自己的脸扯下来
and now I want to rip my face off!
我好像中了诅咒
I think it was cursed.
好 淡定 我们就来
All right, hold tight. We're on our way.
我猜猜
Let me guess.
他碰了不该碰的东西
He touched something he was not supposed to.
必须的
'course he did.
这样
Was, uh…
这样可以了吗
Was that okay?
虽然够不上奥斯卡影帝的水准
Well, not exactly Oscar-worthy, but…
不过也令人信服
…I was convinced.
但这不要紧了
Not that it matters,
你再没话可说了
because you don't have any more lines.
现在做什么
Now what?
现在等着食物上门
Now we wait for meal service.
这样一来
So…
我们又有一具尸体需要处理了
one more body we're gonna have to spirit away, huh?
实际上 不可以
Actually, no.
正如你先前指出的那样
As you so helpfully pointed out earlier,
迪克不喜欢有事见报
Dick doesn't like making the papers.
没错 那我们怎么办
Well, right, so what's the plan?
总不能留下斯考特到处宣扬
Well, we can't have Scott here running his mouth.
大嘴一张 什么都说出去了
Loose lips, yada, yada, yada.
我们得杀了他
We will kill him.
不过别人倒不非得知道他死了
But that doesn't mean anyone ever has to notice he's dead.
收拾东西 乔治
Pack your bags, Georgie.
你要变成斯考特·弗里曼了
You are turning into one Scott Freeman.
要做上三十几年的
for the next, oh, 30-some-odd years.
是不是 斯考特
Right, Scotty?
看来没有受诅咒的镜子了
So much for the cursed mirror.
萨姆和迪恩
Sam and Dean.
很高兴认识二位
It is such a pleasure to make your acquaintances.
为了让你们知道
Now, just so you can put names to the faces.
要吃掉你们的人是谁 我是乔伊斯
that will be eating you, I'm Joyce,
这是我助理 乔治
And this is my assistant, George.
你就是
Oh, you're the …
你是地产公司广告牌上的女人
you're the lady from the real-estate signs.
没错 喜欢我的玉照吗
Yes. You like my photo?
你还是少用点亮白牙线吧
Oh, you might want to lay off the whitening strips.
迪恩啊
Oh, Dean.
我会相当享受把你从牙缝里剔出去的感觉
I am gonna enjoy picking you out of my teeth.
那边有一桶你们喜欢往我们身上泼的东西
There's a bucket of that stuff that you love throwing at us.
就那边
Right there.
趁她没看见 把我按在里面
Dunk me, before she sees.
剑
The sword.
拿剑
The sword!
谢了
Thanks.
我知道这些东西不是闹着玩的
Okay, I get that these things mean business, you know,
但是我不能抬脚就走啊
But I can't just, like, uproot my life.
当然可以
Sure you can.
没你想的那么难
It's not as hard as you'd think.
听着 斯考特
Look, Scott.
这些大嘴怪从不留活口
These big mouths don't like to leave loose ends.
所以你就一直跑 别回头
So don't you look back till you get someplace.
直到你走到语言不通的地方
where you don't speak the language.
好 我这就走
All right. I'm going.
我想该谢谢你们
Hey, thank you, I guess.
别客气
Don't mention it.
给你一分钟
One minute.
解释你为什么帮我们
That's how long you have to explain to us why you helped us.
因为我特别想知道那婆娘什么滋味
Because I am dying to know what that bitch tastes like.
容我理理清 你想吃了你上司
Wait, let me get this straight. You want to eat your boss?
你还有更好的办法阻止她满血复活吗
You got a better way to make her stay dead?
那么 你现在是我们这边的了还是咋的
So, what? So now you're on our side or something?
对
Yeah.
不是的
No.
可乔伊斯要是不死
But if Joyce is alive,
我余生都要收拾她的烂摊子
then I spend the rest of my life cleaning her messes.
或者更惨 被她吃掉
Or worse, I get eaten.
或者自噬
Or bibbed.
所以谢谢二位
So, thanks…
替我把她的头砍下来了
for chopping her head off for me.
单独对付她可不好办
Taking her on solo … yikes.
真的感谢二位帮忙
So, really, thanks for the assist there.
当然了 不用谢
And, of course, you're welcome…
我救了你
for saving you…
不至被她像圣诞礼物那样撕碎
before she ripped into your ass like a christmas present.
双赢 不是吗
Win-win, right?
那么
So.
她的头能给我吗
how 'bout that head?
没门 乔治
Yeah, not gonna happen, Georgie.
说
Now…
迪克·罗曼到底在威斯康星建什么东西
What the hell is Dick Roman building in Wisconsin?
我不知道
I don't know.
我都不知道威斯康星是什么鬼地方
I barely know where Wisconsin is.
我是西海岸的代表
I'm a west-coast representative.
你还会再杀
You gonna keep killing people.
不肯卖房的人吗
who don't sign on the dotted line?
好了 别紧张
All right, take it easy.
杀人不在计划之内
Killing people isn't part of the agenda.
乔伊斯就是有点不耐烦了
Joyce just kept getting impatient.
你们不用担心我的
You got nothing to worry about with me.
你们不懂吗
Don't you get it?
你们紧张错了地方
You guys are freaking out about the wrong thing.
是吗
Oh, you think?
买房卖房这点小事
A couple of real-estate deals?
着眼大局啊 伙计们
Come on. Big picture, guys.
你以为只有这里吗
Y-you think it's just here?
我们到处买地
It's everywhere.
而且比这个小计划要宏伟的多了
And it's a lot more ambitious than this little project.
我建议二位低调些 别出头
My advice … keep your heads down and stay down.
听好了 你个黏糊糊的混蛋
Listen to me, you gooey son of a bitch.
告诉我们你们在这里建什么
You're gonna tell us what you're building here,
要不我就用那个给你漱口
or I'm gonna wash your mouth out with soap.
我还想大家有话好好说呢
Well, I was hoping we could play nice.
如果你们非得知道
But if you must know…
这里要建科研中心
…it's going to be a research center.
研究啥
Research for what?
疾病
Disease.
先生们 我们要在此地治愈癌症
This, gentlemen, is where we are going to cure cancer.
慢着 这说不通啊
Wait. That doesn't make any sense.
迪克·罗曼干嘛要治愈癌症呢
I mean, why would Dick Roman want to cure cancer?
我们就是来普度苍生的
'cause we're only here to help.
怪物治疗癌症
Monsters cure cancer.
真没想到我会说这话
Something I never though I'd say.
真让我不安
Always make me so nervous.
可不是嘛
Yeah, I hear you.
我们现在怎么做
So what do we do now.
你要睡一觉
You're gonna sleep on it.
一直睡到我们到弗兰克那里 懂吗
All the way to Frank's. Capture?
我倒想睡
I wish I could.
你昨晚睡了吗
Did you get any sleep last night?
睡了 一小觉吧 说不好
Yeah, yeah, a little, I-I don't know.
我给你调个温和点的摇滚音乐台
Well, we'll find you a soft-rock station.
一听就睡
Always knocks you right out.
弗兰克
Frank!
德弗罗
Deveraux!
他在里面干嘛呢
What the hell is he doing in there?
弗兰克
Frank!
别开枪 我们要进去了
Don't shoot! We're coming in!
不妙啊
Not good.